const foodWordsEnRu = {
    set_title: "Английские слова: Еда",
    date_of_create: "2023-01-07",
    lang: "ru",
    instructions: "напиши перевод на русский язык",
    category: "изучение английского языка",
    set_cards: [
      {
        question: "Apple",
        answer: "Яблоко",
      },
      {
        question: "Bread",
        answer: "Хлеб",
      },
      {
        question: "Cheese",
        answer: "Сыр",
      },
      {
        question: "Milk",
        answer: "Молоко",
      },
      {
        question: "Egg",
        answer: "Яйцо",
      },
      {
        question: "Chicken",
        answer: "Курица",
      },
      {
        question: "Fish",
        answer: "Рыба",
      },
      {
        question: "Potato",
        answer: "Картофель",
      },
      {
        question: "Carrot",
        answer: "Морковь",
      },
      {
        question: "Soup",
        answer: "Суп",
      },
      {
        question: "Salad",
        answer: "Салат",
      },
      {
        question: "Rice",
        answer: "Рис",
      },
      {
        question: "Pasta",
        answer: "Паста",
      },
      {
        question: "Meat",
        answer: "Мясо",
      },
      {
        question: "Butter",
        answer: "Масло",
      },
    ],
  }
  
  export default foodWordsEnRu;
  